chemistdirect.com.au 2018-04-26

# Privacy Policy

By using the website, you consent to the collection and use by us of any personal and other information you provide whilst using the website in accordance our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the Privacy Policy, please do not use the website.

What sort of information do we collect?

We collect personal information in accordance with the relevant privacy laws in Australia. Personal information is collected about you only on registration or when you visit certain parts of a website where you are invited to provide content, submissions and suggestions or participate in interactive online activities (i.e. community postings, voting, chat, games, or bulletin boards). Personal information can include your name, e-mail address, credit card details, demographic information about you (such as your postcode and age) and any other information of a personal nature which you provide. While we strive to protect our user's personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online and you do so at your own risk.

We also collect non-personal information such as your IP address and use 'cookies' on the website. The information it obtains from collecting IP addresses and using 'cookies' is not personal information about you. For more information, please read the section on IP addresses and cookies below.

How do we use and disclose personal information?

We use personal information to fulfil orders and for feedback purposes (to the extent that is explained when users provide the information), to process e-commerce transactions or to contact you about products or services or send you information that may be of interest to you.

A user's email address will not be posted by us on our website. If we plan to post your personal information on the website, you will be given prior notification of such posting and given the option of preventing such posting.

Please note, if you provide your credit card information to us in order to conduct an e-commerce transaction on the website, we will provide your information to participating merchants in order to process that transaction. We are not responsible for how that information may be used by participating merchants. From time to time we may make our mailing list available to carefully selected companies whose products or services may be of interest to you. If you would prefer not to receive offers from these other companies please let us know at the time of ordering by phone or mail to:

Chemist Direct Privacy Officer  
99 Spring St   
Bondi Junction NSW 2022

Please note that financial information and any information you have provided regarding your health will never be shared.

We will not transfer personal information about you to an organisation outside Australia without your consent. If at any we are required by law or legal process to release personal information about you, we must cooperate fully.

You must be 18 years of age or over to use this site.

How do we keep your personal information secure?

We cannot guarantee, in every circumstance, the security of the personal information you provide on the website. All incoming encrypted information is routed through our firewall, which serves as a gatekeeper for our system. Only data containing the correct authorisation is permitted past the firewall. Attempts to pass the firewall are constantly monitored for suspicious activity.

How do we use IP Addresses and 'Cookies'?

We collect IP addresses for the purposes of system administration and usage analysis of the website and to report aggregated information to its advertisers. We use 'cookies' to track how and when customers use this website. 'Cookies' are used to see which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates are made to the website based on data collected by 'cookies' such as total number of visitors and pages viewed. This information is most easily tracked with cookies. If you accept the first tracking cookie from the website, you won't be offered as many afterwards. If you'd prefer, you can set your web browser to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. However, it is possible that some parts of the website, such as the shopping, contest, and game areas, will not function properly if you do so.

We also use aggregated information (which is information recorded in any form about more than one individual) where the identity of the individual is not known and cannot be inferred from the information. We may use aggregated information to describe our User base to current or potential partners, investors and advertisers; after a survey, to understand and respond to market needs and preferences; or to make recommendations to other Users of our Website.

We work with third parties to serve ads on sites owned or operated by other companies. Our ad servers, and those of our partners, use Cookies and Pixel Tags in order to anonymously identify your browser. Some third-party ad companies, such as ad networks, may combine anonymous information obtained in connection with activity on our Website with information obtained from other sources and/or sites. We do not use or share any personal information with any of our ad server partners, media partners or ad networks without your authorization.

Changes to Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently.
